With the mobile setup web page on
pictotree.eu, you can build your
digital pictogram binder pages.
To build a binder,
you first start by building
the pages of this binder using the tree builder.
Being digital allows you to
put pictograms inside other
pictograms, creating hierarchical trees,
which can be very convenient
in many situations.
Here for example, we have a page
representing a home. The bathroom
is inside the bedroom, and the bathroom
contains several items.
You can also create classic binder pages
with standard linear layouts without
extra dimensions.
The application
allows you to search directly in the
ARASAAC pictogram library
and/or upload and use your own
custom pictograms.
Adding images and modifying trees
is done easily with an intuitive
drag-and-drop interface.
Once your trees are assembled
and saved, you simply place them
into the binder builder, which
represents your complete binder.
Once saved, binders and trees
will be immediately ready to download
directly from the mobile application.